Give thanks to God for what He is about to do in your life.
Give thanks to Him for what He is about to do.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
... for what He is about to do.
Viewers, give thanks to God for what God is about to do in your life.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ’s name we pray.
Thou power of deliverance!
Open your lips.
Let the power of deliverance begin to reign, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to reign, in the name of Jesus!
Power of deliverance – begin to reign, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Where can you go from His presence?
You evil spirit, where can you go from His presence?
You evil spirit, you demon, where can you go from His presence?
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus, I command you to leave my people!
You evil spirit, in the name of Jesus, I command you to leave my people!
Spirit of killing, stealing, destruction – these are not the spirits of God.
I command you out, in the name of Jesus!
You are not the spirit of God; I command you to leave my people!
I command you to leave my people!
Their body, their temple is not your habitat – leave my people!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
At the name of Jesus, at the command of Jesus, leave my people!
You cannot possess my people.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Their body is the temple of the Holy Ghost.
Holy Ghost!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Leave my people – you evil spirit!
Spirit of affliction, leave my people!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You must leave!
Leave!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You must leave!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Leave with your affliction!
Leave with your pain!
Leave with your sickness; leave with your disease – I command, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever pain, whatever affliction – wherever it is in your body, wherever it is in your blood -
I command you to leave, in the name of Jesus!
Watch your screen - there is a clot of blood in what they are vomiting out.
Leave, in the name of Jesus!
There is a poison in some blood, bones, organs -
I command that poison to leave, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located!
Continue to watch your screen, what they are vomiting out is...
Open your lips and begin to command that sickness out.
Command them out, in your blood, fluids, bones, kidney, liver.
Anywhere you are; distance is not a barrier.
You can see what that lady is vomiting out - poisons of different colours, strange things -
that is what has been causing pain and discomfort in their life for so long.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Every voice of pain, of affliction – cease, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
It is the promise of God today to free you – zero affliction, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located – that affliction – begin to flush it out, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips...
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Viewers, ask Jesus to locate you in His mercy.
Locate me in Your mercy, Lord and deliver me!
Locate me in Your mercy and heal me, Lord!
Locate me in Your mercy and free me!
Lord, Jesus, locate me in Your mercy and free me!
Locate me in Your mercy and deliver me!
Locate me in Your mercy and free me!
Mercy!
Locate me in Your mercy and heal me!
Locate me in Your mercy and deliver me!
You are declared free, in the name of Jesus!
Wherever it is located in your body – hear the voice of God!
Where can you go from His presence?
You sickness, where can you go from His presence?
You affliction, where can you go from His presence?
Whatever name they call it – never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
You cancer, affliction – leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ’s name!
You are declared free, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
Begin to talk in your freedom.
Jesus says, “You are healed!”
You are healed!
I say, “You are healed!”
Confess your freedom.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Jesus says you are healed!
You are healed!
I say, you are healed,
in the name of Jesus Christ!
Begin to seal your blessing with the Blood of Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus Christ!
If there is any affliction among you – within, outside -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Be completely delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, begin to see yourself the way God sees you -
a person without affliction, hardship, stagnation, career failure!
Begin to see yourself the way God sees you, right now.
See yourself the way God sees you.
A person without hardship, stagnation, career failure, nightmare – this is the way God sees you.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Right now, remember your nation, your country.
God’s intervention!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Remember your leaders – God’s wisdom.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Right now, cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus.
Viewers all over the world, cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus.
Cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus.
In Jesus Christ’s name we pray.
Right now, for those who want to rededicate themselves,
coming here for the first time, seeing Jesus walking in the Spirit, in His name;
right now open your lips and say,
Lord Jesus, come into my heart.
Wash me with Your precious Blood.
Lord Jesus, make me Your channel – Your channel of truth where there is falsehood.
Make me Your channel of truth, Your channel of forgiveness, Your channel of pardon,
Your channel of love.
Lord Jesus, thank You for dying in my place.
Thank You for Your salvation.
In Jesus Christ’s name!
Right now, accept Him.
Thank Him as a channel of truth, love, faithfulness, pardon, forgiveness.
Begin to thank Him.
Thank Him for allowing you to stand for Him.
Thank Him.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 05/10/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 06/10/2018